Andras Egyed

7+ years of experience in the healthcare sector with degreebased education and managing private care institutions. Selftrained web developer with 2 years project-based practice in website and app creation. Active curiosity for tech, coding and complex data challenges, striving for new work responsibilities that align with my passion.



DEVELOPMENT EXPERIENCE



2020 - Present

Udemy / Self-study

- Completing Udemy`s The Complete Web Development Bootcamp
- Evolved trained knowledge by extending functionalities of courseincluded existing projects as well as initiating own projects
- Re-worked existing UGC blog page by adding features (e.g. implementation of user authentification, swipe interactions), changing navigation and structure for a smoother user experience
- · Created a crud application with Firebase backend with multiple authentication options including otp text confirmation
- Built a dynamic portfolio web-page, inspired by an existing design, that compiles all of my signature projects whilst applying new features such as lazy embedding and pop-state manipulation

WORK EXPERIENCE



2021 - Present

Deputy Manager / Care Coordinator

- Quality Management to guarantee achievement of business
- Ensure compliance with internal systems, procedures and policies
- Staff management and leadership
- Organisation and execution of staff trainings
- Key POC for clients, relatives and representatives as well as social workers, doctors, nurses and local councils
- Budget planning
- Regular workstream, risk and quality analysis to support business growth using Advanced Care Management Software (Staffplan)
- Monitoring documentation updates
- Senior Management reports
- Payroll & invoicing

CONTACT



07784834222



egyeand@gmail.com



in linkedin.com/in/egyeand



github.com/AndrasE



andrasegyed.netlify.app

EXPERTISE

HTML	85%
css	75%
BS	65%
JS	75%
REACT	60%

ACQUAINTANCES

- Node.js
- Body-parser
- Encryption
- Authentication
- SQL
- MongoDb
- Express.js
- Passport.js
- Hammer.js
- APIs
- NoSQL
- Firebase

WORK EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

2020 - Present

Care Coordinator

- Allocation of care and support workers to all client visits using a combination of Staffplan software and PASS system
- Documentation of all workstreams
- Keeping electronic client- and care worker records up to date
- Creation and implementation of management information and processes
- · Maintaining computer systems up to date
- Ensuring compliance with all office systems and procedures
- Creation of reports and statistical analysis for senior management

2018 - 2019

Field Care Supervisor

- Monitor, supervise and mentor all care and support workers
- Facilitate practical inductions of all new care and support workers
- · Assessment of individual client needs and potential risks
- · Onboarding and training of staff
- Ensure accuracy and completeness of documentation
- Emotional and practical support to individuals and their families
- Be on-call in case of an emergency

= 2012 - 2018

Various Positions

The decision and execution in moving to the United Kingdom came with multiple challenges, particularly in regards to language and transferrable skills and education. So I set foot in this new country by trying a variety of generic service and logistical jobs, such as working as a shop assistant, gardener, support worker and many more.

= 2010 - 2011

School Teacher (Arts)

- Teaching art in the 5th and 6th grade classes
- Organizing exercises of day-border students
- Organization and execution of school events
- Pedagogical support and advise for children as well as parents
- Creative working training

INTERESTS













EDUCATION

2021 - 2022 Udemy Inc.

The Complete 2022 Web Development Bootcamp

Comprehensive course covering both front and back end, various languages and libraries.

2019 - 2020 Highfield Qualifications

L5 Management and leadership in healthcare

Credit-based diploma focusing on Leadership & Management within a health and social care setting

苗 2016 - 2017 Impact Futures

L3 Diploma in health and social care

Gaining underpinning knowledge and understanding and demonstrate competence in healthcare settings

2005 - 2009 KTIF

Bachelor's Degree School Teacher – Arts

Main subjects: Pedagogy and Psychology

Other core subjects: Science, Mathematics, Humanities, Arts, Technology and Computing

2016- 2017 University of Debrecen

Mathematics and Informatics (2 semester)

Achieved practical knowledge in Algebra, Linear Algebra, Mathematical logic and Introduction to Analysis

SKILLS

- Analytical thinking
- Project management
- Eye for detail
- Flexibility and quick adoption
- Problem solving
- "Lets do it" mentality
- Complex task coordination